VERONIKA HARBACHOVA

Austin, TX 78701 | 734.834.2893 | veronika.har@hotmail.com

Profile Summary

Linguist turned web developer blends soft skills of adaptability and openmindedness with hard skills of web design. Cross-functional collaboration with tech teams and successful experience of working as a part of one. Experience in logistics honed my problem-solving, analytical and leadership skills.

Experience

Freelance Web Developer - 12/2018 - now

- Portfolio website: https://veronikaharbachova.netlify.com/;
- ✓ 10+ projects using React, Node, Vue, Angular etc. Currently working on a collaboration project of a cross-platform archery mobile app;
- ✓ A project example: a movie web app that requires users to create an account to access information on movies, directors, genres, add/remove favorite movies to the profile, edit/delete their account info. The app uses RESTful API. Front-end done with React, Redux and Bootstrap. Back-end done with Node and MongoDB.

Wallenborn Transports S.A – Luxembourg, Luxembourg

Supply Chain Specialist | 02/2015 - 07/2016

Lear Corporation – *Shanghai, China* Supply Chain Specialist | 11/2013 – 06/2014

Generation_P – Minsk, Belarus

XSLT developer / Assistant Team-Leader | 09/2007 - 08/2008

- ✓ Achieved full technical competency in 3 months without any prior experience (CVS repo; PAROS (POST/GET); Oxygen+Eclipse; XML etc);
- ✓ Assistant Team-Leader supervised team performing patch-and-release responsibilities and negotiated business solutions with foreign customers.

Education

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

CareerFoundry | 01/2019 - 11/2019

- 300+ hours of training/mentoring with industry leading Front-End and Senior Full-Stack Web Developer.
- Intensive project-based training program with a focus on JavaScript, HTML, CSS and most prominent libraries, frameworks and tools;

Master of Arts in Linguistics

Dalian University of Technology | 09/2008 - 07/2011

Bachelor of Arts in Linguistics

Belarusian State University | 09/2003 - 06/2008

Skills

React.js

Redux

React Native

Node.js

jQuery

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

PWA

REST API

Bootstrap

Responsive Design

TDD

Toolkit

NPM

TypeScript

Sass

Jest / Enzyme

MongoDB

Heroku

CodePen

Git / GitHub

Chrome Developer

Tools

Photoshop

Languages

English

Russian

Italian

Mandarin Chinese

Ukranian

Belarusian